let hardsubtractionquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 148 - 3",
        AnswerA: "142",
        AnswerB: "143",
        AnswerC: "144",
        AnswerD: "145",
        correctAnswer: "145",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 133 - 14",
        AnswerA: "117",
        AnswerB: "118",
        AnswerC: "119",
        AnswerD: "120",
        correctAnswer: "119",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 143 - 12",
        AnswerA: "121",
        AnswerB: "122",
        AnswerC: "123",
        AnswerD: "124",
        correctAnswer: "121",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 138 - 16",
        AnswerA: "120",
        AnswerB: "121",
        AnswerC: "122",
        AnswerD: "123",
        correctAnswer: "122",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 147 - 13",
        AnswerA: "133",
        AnswerB: "134",
        AnswerC: "135",
        AnswerD: "136",
        correctAnswer: "134",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 145 - 22",
        AnswerA: "122",
        AnswerB: "123",
        AnswerC: "124",
        AnswerD: "125",
        correctAnswer: "123",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 139 - 7",
        AnswerA: "130",
        AnswerB: "131",
        AnswerC: "132",
        AnswerD: "133",
        correctAnswer: "132",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 146 - 5",
        AnswerA: "141",
        AnswerB: "142",
        AnswerC: "143",
        AnswerD: "144",
        correctAnswer: "141",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 149 - 17",
        AnswerA: "130",
        AnswerB: "131",
        AnswerC: "132",
        AnswerD: "133",
        correctAnswer: "132",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 146 - 4",
        AnswerA: "142",
        AnswerB: "143",
        AnswerC: "144",
        AnswerD: "145",
        correctAnswer: "142",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 137 - 6",
        AnswerA: "131",
        AnswerB: "132",
        AnswerC: "133",
        AnswerD: "134",
        correctAnswer: "131",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 125 - 15",
        AnswerA: "107",
        AnswerB: "108",
        AnswerC: "109",
        AnswerD: "110",
        correctAnswer: "110",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 - 17",
        AnswerA: "116",
        AnswerB: "117",
        AnswerC: "118",
        AnswerD: "119",
        correctAnswer: "119",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 123 - 18",
        AnswerA: "105",
        AnswerB: "106",
        AnswerC: "107",
        AnswerD: "108",
        correctAnswer: "105",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 119 - 7",
        AnswerA: "111",
        AnswerB: "112",
        AnswerC: "113",
        AnswerD: "114",
        correctAnswer: "112",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 147 - 35",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "112",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 134 - 28",
        AnswerA: "104",
        AnswerB: "105",
        AnswerC: "106",
        AnswerD: "107",
        correctAnswer: "106",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 133 - 32",
        AnswerA: "100",
        AnswerB: "101",
        AnswerC: "102",
        AnswerD: "103",
        correctAnswer: "101",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 114 - 11",
        AnswerA: "102",
        AnswerB: "103",
        AnswerC: "104",
        AnswerD: "105",
        correctAnswer: "103",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 138 - 27",
        AnswerA: "108",
        AnswerB: "109",
        AnswerC: "110",
        AnswerD: "111",
        correctAnswer: "111",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 148 - 38",
        AnswerA: "110",
        AnswerB: "111",
        AnswerC: "112",
        AnswerD: "113",
        correctAnswer: "110",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 - 16",
        AnswerA: "117",
        AnswerB: "118",
        AnswerC: "119",
        AnswerD: "120",
        correctAnswer: "120",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 117 - 5",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "112",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 137 - 9",
        AnswerA: "125",
        AnswerB: "126",
        AnswerC: "127",
        AnswerD: "128",
        correctAnswer: "128",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 143 - 27",
        AnswerA: "114",
        AnswerB: "115",
        AnswerC: "116",
        AnswerD: "117",
        correctAnswer: "117",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 149 - 36",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "113",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 122 - 8",
        AnswerA: "113",
        AnswerB: "114",
        AnswerC: "115",
        AnswerD: "116",
        correctAnswer: "114",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 - 28",
        AnswerA: "105",
        AnswerB: "106",
        AnswerC: "107",
        AnswerD: "108",
        correctAnswer: "108",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 150 - 50",
        AnswerA: "100",
        AnswerB: "105",
        AnswerC: "110",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "100",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 127 - 13",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "114",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 138 - 29",
        AnswerA: "107",
        AnswerB: "108",
        AnswerC: "109",
        AnswerD: "111",
        correctAnswer: "109",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 131 - 17",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "114",
    },
]